<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Jim Crist-Harif - ramblings</title><link href="https://jcristharif.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://jcristharif.com/feeds/ramblings.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://jcristharif.com/</id><updated>2020-03-20T14:30:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>A Farewell to Anaconda</title><link href="https://jcristharif.com/farewell-to-anaconda.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-03-20T14:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-20T14:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Jim Crist</name></author><id>tag:jcristharif.com,2020-03-20:/farewell-to-anaconda.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;A recap on my last 5 years at Anaconda&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the spring of 2015 I quit my graduate program and moved to TX to work for
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.anaconda.com/"&gt;Anaconda&lt;/a&gt; (then Continuum Analytics). Graduate
school hadn't been great for my mental health, and increasingly I was finding
the thing I liked most about my research was the software development aspects
of it. I was thrilled to be hired to help maintain the Python scientific
ecosystem full time. It was my dream job, which is why it feels so hard to say
that it's time to move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today is my last day at Anaconda. I'm not leaving for any particular reason, it
just feels like it's time. I've never quit a job before, every job I've had has
had a set end time (e.g. &amp;quot;I'm going back to grad school&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;we can't dig holes
anymore because the ground is frozen&amp;quot;). It feels weird, but I'm excited for
what's next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm proud of the work I helped accomplish at Anaconda. We helped create (and
maintain) open source software that is used by thousands. Here I thought I'd
recap a few of my highlights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="dask"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Dask&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;img title="Dask is not an acronym, our logo is just shouting its name" class="align-center" src="/images/dask-logo-horizontal.svg" style="width: 80%;" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of my work for the last 5 years has been related (in one way or another)
to &lt;a class="reference external" href="https.dask.org"&gt;Dask&lt;/a&gt;. I first started contributing while in graduate
school (~5 years ago today!). I had met Matt Rocklin the previous fall at the &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://lwn.net/Articles/618282/"&gt;Google Summer of Code
reunion&lt;/a&gt;, where he &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://xkcd.com/356/"&gt;nerd-sniped&lt;/a&gt; me into what ended up being a multi-month obsession
with term-rewriting systems (I was interested in adding one to &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.sympy.org"&gt;SymPy&lt;/a&gt; at the time). So the following spring, when Dask
needed some rewrite-rules for it's optimizer &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/dask/dask/issues/79"&gt;I was happy to help&lt;/a&gt;). Thus began a career of hopelessly
understimating how long it takes to do things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img title="So young, so naive." class="align-center" src="/images/first-dask-issue-comment.png" style="width: 90%;" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The code for this still lives in &lt;tt class="docutils literal"&gt;dask.rewrite&lt;/tt&gt; (docs &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://docs.dask.org/en/latest/optimize.html#rewrite-rules"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;), although
it's no longer used internally. Dask has grown up a lot since then. It's now a
whole ecosystem, with
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://anaconda.com"&gt;multiple&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://coiled.io/"&gt;companies&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.quansight.com/"&gt;invested in&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://rapids.ai/"&gt;its development&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.saturncloud.io/"&gt;and maintenance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm still planning on continuuing work on Dask outside of Anaconda, and am
excited to see how the project evolves over the next 5 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="datashader"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Datashader&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideas behind what would become &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://datashader.org/"&gt;Datashader&lt;/a&gt;
(then called &amp;quot;abstract rendering&amp;quot;) were first described to me at a conference
happy hour by &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://twitter.com/pwang"&gt;Peter Wang&lt;/a&gt;. It sounded
interesting - a mix of &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://dask.org/"&gt;dask&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://numba.org"&gt;numba&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://bokeh.org/"&gt;bokeh&lt;/a&gt; - the perfect
demonstration of all the neat libraries Continuum was helping develop at the
time. I took a few weeks off from Dask development and helped write the first
version (hopefully most of my code has been rewritten at this point). It made
some pretty plots (here's an example with NYC Census data):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img title="NYC Census, categorized by race" class="align-center" src="/images/datashader-nyc-census.png" style="width: 90%;" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashader was my first real experience developing a production library from
scratch. It worked, it was speedy, but I spent too long waffling about how the
API should be written (I think I rewrote the user-facing API 3-4 times). This
whole experience helped me learn that sometimes it's best to get things in
front of users and iterate, rather than developing &amp;quot;the perfect API&amp;quot; from the
get-go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="python-hadoop"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Python &amp;amp; Hadoop&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my time at Anaconda I did a few consulting projects deploying and using
Dask, mostly at large institutions. This was a useful exercise, as it revealed
many pain points when integrating with enterprise-y systems (read Hadoop). I
think it's easy for open-source devs to miss key issues if they're not also
direct users of their software. Things you might not expect to cause issues
often do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One issue that kept cropping up was Hadoop integration. Many of our customers
had purchased large Hadoop/YARN clusters, and we had no way to run our software
on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img title="sometimes things are difficult" class="align-center" src="/images/one-does-not-simply-deploy-on-yarn.jpg" style="width: 60%;" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While we primarily wanted to be able to run Dask on
these clusters, we also wanted a general solution. This led to &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jcristharif.com/skein/"&gt;Skein&lt;/a&gt;, a (hopefully) user-friendly tool for
deploying and managing applications on Hadoop/YARN (&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jcristharif.com/introducing-skein.html"&gt;blogpost here&lt;/a&gt;). While Skein was developed primarily for use in &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://yarn.dask.org"&gt;dask-yarn&lt;/a&gt;, it's also used by several other projects:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://ray.readthedocs.io/en/latest/deploy-on-yarn.html"&gt;Ray&lt;/a&gt; - another distributed computing project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/criteo/tf-yarn"&gt;tf-yarn&lt;/a&gt; - deploys tensorflow on YARN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jupyterhub-yarnspawner.readthedocs.io"&gt;jupyterhub-yarnspawner&lt;/a&gt; - deploys JupyterHub on YARN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://gateway.dask.org/"&gt;dask-gateway&lt;/a&gt; - a managed deployment solution for Dask&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skein is a Python wrapper around a Java application, which meant I had to learn
Java. YARN is also mostly undocumented, which meant I had to read its source to
understand the internals (and the &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://steveloughran.gitbooks.io/kerberos_and_hadoop/"&gt;madness beyond the gate&lt;/a&gt;). As a result of
this I am now:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A pretty mediocre Java developer (all of Skein looks like a Python developer
writing Java, which is accurate).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fairly knowledgable about the internals of a mostly legacy system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future employers be warned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="jupyterhub-on-hadoop"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;JupyterHub on Hadoop&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuuing my rage against enterprise systems, I grew frustrated with
Cloudera's datascience workbench and developed a way to natively run
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jupyterhub.readthedocs.io"&gt;JupyterHub&lt;/a&gt; on Hadoop. It works, there's
&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jupyterhub-on-hadoop.readthedocs.io/en/latest/"&gt;docs and everything&lt;/a&gt;. I even made a
walkthrough video:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style="text-align:center"&gt;
  &lt;iframe
    width="640"
    height="385"
    src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M7T8Xnj9M6c"
    frameborder="0"
    allow="autoplay; encrypted-media;"
    allowfullscreen&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This mostly involved:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing an spawner: &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jupyterhub-yarnspawner.readthedocs.io"&gt;yarnspawner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing an authenticator: &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jupyterhub-kerberosauthenticator.readthedocs.io"&gt;kerberosauthenticator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing a contents-manager: &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://jcristharif.com/hdfscm/"&gt;hdfscm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documenting everything and hoping it's useful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JupyterHub is a wonderfully designed project and is a pleasure to work on. The
Jupyter community is also a model of what community-driven development can
accomplish. May Dask's community one day be equally be as open and supportive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="dask-gateway"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Dask-Gateway&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dask's existing deployment solutions work well, but are inherently
decentralized. They require users to have direct access to the underlying
cluster system (e.g. Kubernetes RBAC permissions), as well as network access to
all nodes in the cluster (firewalls be damned). Likewise, users are expected to
have some knowledge of the underlying systems (e.g. K8s pod specs), which makes
onboarding trickier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://gateway.dask.org"&gt;Dask-Gateway&lt;/a&gt; is our attempt at providing a
managed solution. It allows users to launch and use Dask clusters in a shared,
centrally managed cluster environment, without requiring users to have
knowledge of or direct access to the underlying cluster backend (e.g.
Kubernetes, Hadoop/YARN, HPC Job queues, etc…). In short, &amp;quot;Dask clusters as a
service&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img title="dask-gateway's architecture" class="align-center" src="/images/dask-gateway-architecture.svg" style="width: 80%;" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dask-Gateway feels like a culmination of the previous work I've done:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's a solution for deploying &lt;em&gt;Dask&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It works on multiple backends, including &lt;em&gt;Hadoop/YARN&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It looks a lot like &lt;em&gt;JupyterHub&lt;/em&gt; (it's basically JupyterHub, but for Dask)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project (like any project) has been a great opportunity to learn. Before
this I had never written a serious web application, now I have &lt;em&gt;opinions&lt;/em&gt; about
Python asyncio server frameworks. I also got a lot of experience working with
Enterprise Users™ whose needs and security restrictions often differ from the
usual users I encounter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dask-Gateway is currently deployed at a handful of companies, as well as
actively used as part of the &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://pangeo.io"&gt;Pangeo Project&lt;/a&gt;. I just
finished a major rewrite of the server internals, and plan to keep developing
it in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="retrospective"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Retrospective&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The projects discussed above don't encompass everything I've done while working
at Anaconda, but they're a sampling of my favorites. My job for the past 5
years has been to maintain and better the Python ecosystem, and in that I hope
I've been successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But Anaconda is more than just the software we made along the way. It's a
company full of brilliant and kind people who care about their work and the
community they're supporting. I will miss the people most.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks Anaconda for a great 5 years, I truly wish you all the best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="what-s-next"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What's Next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm excited to say I'm going to work at &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.prefect.io/"&gt;Prefect&lt;/a&gt;.
There (among a myriad of other things), I hope to improve Prefect's integration
with Dask. I'll also be given time to continue maintenance and development of
the Dask ecosystem (bringing Prefect into the fold of companies maintaining
Dask :) ).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before then I'm taking a few weeks off to relax. I'm returning my work laptop
to Anaconda today, and will only have access to my old college laptop (2 GiB of
RAM!) until my new job starts. Call it a forced detox from OSS development. I
have a few woodworking projects and books to keep me busy, and am looking
forward to the break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="ramblings"></category></entry><entry><title>Reading List, 2017</title><link href="https://jcristharif.com/reading-2017.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-01-01T12:30:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-01-01T12:30:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Jim Crist</name></author><id>tag:jcristharif.com,2018-01-01:/reading-2017.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Everything I read in 2017&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Growing up I used to read &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt;, but fell out of habit during college due to
lack of time. This year my new year's resolution was to read again. I set a
goal of reading 26 books (1 every 2 weeks), and managed to exceed that by 3.
Going to shoot for 30 in 2018 :). Here it is, everything I read in 2017:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Martian&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Andy Weir (1/1/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Metamorphasis&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Franz Kafka (1/8/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Infinite Jest&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; David Foster Wallace(1/31/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Hunter S. Thompson (2/5/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Clockwork Orange&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Anthony Burgess (2/10/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blood Meridian&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Cormac McCarthy (2/25/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cats Cradle&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Kurt Vonnegut (3/9/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Crying of Lot 49&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Thomas Pynchon (3/18/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;To Say Nothing of the Dog&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Connie Willis (3/28/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beloved&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Toni Morrison (4/18/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Sirens of Titan&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Kurt Vonnegut (5/5/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kafka on the Shore&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Haruki Murakami (5/28/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Great Gatsby&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; F. Scott Fitzgerald (6/12/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;One Day in the Life of Ivan Denisovich&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn (6/15/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Catcher in the Rye&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; J. D. Salinger (7/4/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Homegoing&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Yaa Gyasi (7/9/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Player Piano&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Kurt Vonnegut (7/30/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Man in the High Castle&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Phillip K. Dick (8/13/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mother Night&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Kurt Vonnegut (8/18/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Windup Girl&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Paolo Bacigalupi (9/3/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Of Mice and Men&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; John Steinbeck (9/4/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Breakfast of Champions&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Kurt Vonnegut (9/27/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bluest Eye&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Toni Morrison (10/1/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;To Kill a Mockingbird&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Harper Lee (10/16/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Brave New World&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Aldous Huxley (10/29/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wolf in White Van&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; John Darnielle (11/5/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Kurt Vonnegut (12/5/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Ocean at the End of the Lane&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Neil Gaiman (12/23/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sula&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash; Toni Morrison (12/31/2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at the timeline, I read the most when I was flying (been traveling for
work more frequently). There's also a few blank spots where I started a book
and gave up on it (most recently retried &lt;em&gt;As I Lay Dying&lt;/em&gt; by Faulkner, and
I still can't get through it).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few highlights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Infinite Jest&lt;/em&gt; is a trope, but was still one of the best books I've ever
  read. I started it in 2016 and for a few months carried that 10 lb book
  everywhere, doubling as an exercise routine. Recommend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I read a good portion of Kurt Vonnegut's works this year. His pointed humor
  is still relevant 50 years later. Top picks: &lt;em&gt;Cat's Cradle&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;God Bless
  You Mr. Rosewater&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In high school we read one Toni Morrison book (Sula), and I didn't care for
  it then. Coming back to her 10 years later I now like her style (her content
  has depth and her descriptions are vivid without being overwhelming). If you
  read anything by her I recommend &lt;em&gt;The Bluest Eye&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To Say Nothing of the Dog&lt;/em&gt; by Connie Willis is one of the funniest books
  I've ever read. Every book Connie Willis has written has been nominated for
  (and usually won) the Hugo award for best novel. She's fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wolf in White Van&lt;/em&gt; by John Darnielle (of &lt;em&gt;The Mountain Goats&lt;/em&gt;) was
  surprisingly good. I've loved his lyrics, but other musician-turned-authors
  haven't always been as appealing. I've also been enjoying the podcast &lt;em&gt;I Only
  Listen to The Mountain Goats&lt;/em&gt; by him and Joseph Fink (of &lt;em&gt;Welcome to
  Nightvale&lt;/em&gt;), although that may only appeal to fans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn't particularly care for &lt;em&gt;Blood Meridian&lt;/em&gt;. Cormac McCarthy writes
  stunning descriptions of landscapes and vague descriptions of characters.
  This one takes place in Texas and is mildly historical, so it was neat to tie
  scene's to places I've been, but didn't make up for the book's deficiencies.
  It was also way darker than &lt;em&gt;The Road&lt;/em&gt;, which I didn't think was possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I read &lt;em&gt;The Ocean at the End of the Lane&lt;/em&gt; in one sitting. Neil Gaiman is
  consistently great. Reminded me a bit of the dark childhood tales Roald Dahl
  is known for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Homegoing&lt;/em&gt; was on this year's &lt;a href="https://undergrad.stanford.edu/advising/approaching-stanford/three-books"&gt;Stanford 3 book
  list&lt;/a&gt;
  (for incoming freshman), and is the most recently published book I read. I
  loved it enough to mail it to my sister, who's passing it on. Recommend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><category term="Ramblings"></category><category term="ramblings"></category></entry></feed>